我等了你10分钟 下不为例
l've been waiting for you 10 minutes. Don't do that again.
这件衣服使我看起来
This dress makes me look
像一个沃尔沃思灯罩
like a wulworth lampshade.
我不穿这个
l'm not wearing this.
我叫你穿你就穿
You wear it because l tell you to wear it.
我才不穿呢
l'm not wearing this dress.
当安迪出庭作证的时候
And when Andy's on the stand,
我希望你拿件毛衣出来打
l want you be knitting.
打毛衣 噢 看在上帝的份上
Knitting? For Christ's sake.
打一件婴儿衣服
-A baby garment.
我不会打毛衣
l don't know how to knit!
那就学
Then learn.
那样没办法得到陪审团的同情
That's no way to win the jury's sympathy.
哦 你不想听我的意见了
You don't need advice anymore?
你看这儿 代言人先生
Look at here, Mr. Mouthpiece.
在我看来我才是哪个
lt seems to me that l am the one
想出好点子的人
who's coming up with the good ideas.
我讨厌每个人都告诉我该怎么做
l'm sick of everybody telling me what to do.